A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
The Library of Virginia
36853, 37349, 43628, 44118, 44828
218 cu. ft. (218 boxes)
LVA
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 36853, transferred on 29 September 1999.
Accession 37349, transferred on 26 May 2000.
Accession 43628, transferred on 18 February 2008.
Accession 44118, transferred on 4 February 2009.
Accession 44828, transferred on 24 February 2010.
Historical Information
On March 29, 1877, the General Assembly passed an act creating the Department of Agriculture, Mining, and Manufacturing to compile a geological handbook, analyze soils and fertilizers, dispense information to agriculturists in the state, and distribute seeds provided by the federal government. The Board of Agriculture was established by the General Assembly on March 5, 1888, to manage the department. The name of the department was changed to the Department of Agriculture and Immigration by an act passed on February 25, 1908, and the agency was given the additional mission of promoting the immigration of farmers into the state. On March 27, 1914, the General Assembly made the commissioner of the department a member of the Convict Lime Grinding Board. This board, which supervised the employment of state penitentiary convicts at state lime grinding plants, was abolished by the state government reorganization act passed by the General Assembly on April 18, 1927, and its duties were transferred to the Board of Agriculture and Immigration.
A major shift in focus occurred when, in a statewide referendum held on November 1, 1966, the voters approved a proposed constitutional amendment passed by the General Assembly on March 11 that changed the name of the department to the Department of Agriculture and Commerce. The governor issued a proclamation of the name change on November 30, 1966, and on March 4, 1971, the General Assembly passed an act codifying the change. The name of the department was changed to the Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services by an act passed by the General Assembly on March 24, 1978.
The Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, which oversees the department, consists of eleven members, one from each congressional district. Seven of the members must be farmers. The members are appointed by the governor for four-year terms and confirmed by the Senate. The presidents of Virginia State University and Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University are ex-officio members of the board. The board is responsible for policy formulation on matters of agricultural and consumer concern.
Scope and Content
Correspondence and subject files of the Commissioner of the Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services document the planning, direction, and implementation of agency programs and are evidence of actions and policy decisions. These records include correspondence, subject files, board and committee meeting records, minutes, memoranda, news clippings, newsletters, and reports.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 1984-1993 (bulk 1990-1993) (Accession 36853)., 58 cu. ft. (58 boxes)
    This accession is arranged in no discernable order, though there are several alphabetical sequences throughout.
    - Accidents involving state owned vehicles, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Africanized honey bee, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - AG Diversification Conference (Lynchburg), 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agreements, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Agribusiness Council, Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agribusiness Parks, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agriculture, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agriculture in the classroom, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Agricultural Hall of Fame, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agricultural Opportunities Commission, 1980. (Box 1)
    - Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Aldicarb, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Agricultural Movement of Virginia, 1984-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Dairy Association, 1988-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Dairy Association of Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - American Sheep Federation, 1990. (Box 1)
    - Angola, 1987-1991. (Box 1)
    - Animal Damage Control Program, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Appropriation Committee - House of Delegates, 1984-1990. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Executive Committee, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Junior Scholarship Program, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Premiums Committee, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Program briefing, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Bees, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Biotechnology Task Force, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Carroll County Farmers Market, 1989. (Box 1)
    - Center for Rural Development, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Central Farmers Market, 1989. (Box 1)
    - Certified Seed Board, State - Meeting, 1991 Dec. (Box 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay (general information), 1991. (Box 1)
    - Chincoteague, Town of, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Civil Rights, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Clean Air Act, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Clean Water Act, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Cockfighting, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Code Commission, Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Colonial Farm Credit (Earl Longest), 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Council on the Environment - Scoping Oil/Gas, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Administration and Planning, Division of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Combined Charitable Campaign, 1990-1991. (Box 2)
    - Commission on Population Growth, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Communication, Office of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Comptroller, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1989-1991. (Box 2)
    - Conservation Leadership Project, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, Division of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Advisory Board - Meeting, 1991 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Cotton Gin (general information), 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council of Information Management, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on the Environment, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on State Governments, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on the Environment - Meeting, 1991 June. (Box 2)
    - Coyote control, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Dairy Tour (Harrisonburg), 1991 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Deer farming, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry, Inc., 1989-1991. (Box 2)
    - Delmarva Chicken Festival, 1991 June. (Box 2)
    - Desert Storm, 1991. (Box 2)
    - New Uses Council, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Assistant Attorney General, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Consumer Affairs, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Foods, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Facilities Coordinator, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Finance Office, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Fiscal Manager, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Herb Hill - Strategic planning, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Human Resources - Assistant Director, 1989-1991. (Box 3)
    - Human Resources - Director, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Information Systems, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Internal Auditor, 1991. (Box 3)
    - )Longworth meeting, 1991 May. (Box 3)
    - Purchasing Director, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Virginia Solicitation of Contributions, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Health, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Care position paper, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Health, Southwest Virginia Advisory Committee on, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Wardens, 1988. (Box 3)
    - Animal Welfare issues, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza Outbreak, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Duck/Bird kill in Southeast Virginia, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Egg Quality Assurance Council, 1990. (Box 3)
    - Equine Infectious Anemia Advisory Committee, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Humane treatment at horse auctions, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Managing Avian Influenza and other poultry diseases, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Meat and Poultry Inspection, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council, 1991 June. (Box 3)
    - Pseudorabies Virus Committee, 1987-1991. (Box 3)
    - National Consumers Week, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Marketing Division, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Finvest Foods, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Forest Products Specialist, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - International Marketing, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Wine Marketing Specialish, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Meeting with Robert Gomperts, 1991. (Box 4)
    - International Marketing staff meeting, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Southwest Virginia Farmers Market Board, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Legislative Trail Ride, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Direct Leave Share Pilot Program, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Drought, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Drought in California, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Weekly reports to Secretary Framme, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 Mar. (Box 4)
    - Equine Marketing of Virginia, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 June. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 July. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Plan, Virginia, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Farmers Market Study, 1985. (Box 4)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1988-1991. (Box 4)
    - Farm bill, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Endangered Plants/Species/Insects, 1991. (Box 4)
    - EEO Advisory Committee, 1991-1992. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Impact Statements, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Economic Recovery - Virginia, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Economic Recovery Commission, Virginia (HJR 433), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Earth Day 1990, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Economic Development, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Film Office, Virginia, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry Task Force, Southside (House Document 42), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry School Study, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Commissioner's Agriculture Forum, 1991 May. (Box 5)
    - Food and Libations Association of Virginia (FLAVA), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Furadan (general information), 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Foreign Agricultural Investment, 1984-1991. (Box 5)
    - Future Farmers of American, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal legislators, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Farm Credit Council, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal legislation, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Food Watch, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal-State Marketing Improvement, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Friends of Industry and Agriculture (FIA), 1983-1991. (Box 5)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's European Trade Mission, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Pacific Rim Mission, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Open House, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Report of Rural Development, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Ginseng, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Groundwater, 1991. (Box 5)
    - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT), 1989-1991. (Box 5)
    - Granville P. Mead (Trust), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hemp, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Holiday Blanket Campaign, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hotel information, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Horse Breeder Incentive Program, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Horses (general information), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Horticulture Society, Virginia State, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Incentive Pay Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - JLARC, 1991. (Box 5)
    - IUG Charter, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Information Technoloty, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Kuwait, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Lab Services Management Study, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Lamb Cooperative, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Livestock Export Facility (Blackstone), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Farm Winery Law, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hong Kong/Tokyo Office information, 1989-1990. (Box 5)
    - News clippings, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Policy Analysis and Development, Division of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Food Distribution Section, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Pesticide Managemtn, Office of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Product and Industry Regulation, Division of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - PAIR Assistant Director, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Potato hearing, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Gypsy Moth (general information), 1991. (Box 6)
    - Weights and Measure (Virginia Beach), 1990-1991. (Box 6)
    - Boll Weevil Eradication Program, 1988-1991. (Box 6)
    - Weights and Measures Association meeting, 1991 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Seed Laboratory Services, 1985-1991. (Box 6)
    - SFIREG, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Pesticide appeal, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agricultural Statistics Service, 1990-1991. (Box 6)
    - VDACS/State Boards and Commissions, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Crops and Livestock (newsletter), 1989-1991. (Box 6)
    - Proposed 1990-1991 Budget Addenda, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - EEO/Affirmative Action, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Press Report on Animal Health and Seed Testing Lab, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Information Users Group, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Abingdon/Roanoke Office, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Biennium Budget 1992-1994 (information), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Furlough Task Force, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Budget Reduction 6% (1991-1992), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Task Group on Information Function, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Budget - Revised Appropriation Act, 1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Marketing Accomplishments, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - James City Farmers Market, 1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Temporary Workforce Reduction Plan, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Early Retirement issues and concerns, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Legislative Proposals, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. - Deputy Commissioner, 1992. (Box 7)
    - Organization and Management Study, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG) - meeting, 1991 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG) - meeting, 1991 Aug. (Box 7)
    - Migrant/Seasonal Farm Workers Board, 1989-1991. (Box 7)
    - Market Basket Food Price Surveys, 1982-1991. (Box 7)
    - Migrant Worker Policy Committee, Interagency, 1990. (Box 7)
    - Nottoway Teaching/Demonstration Farm, 1989-1991. (Box 7)
    - National Governors Association, 1991. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - grant, 1991-1992. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Mexico Agricultural Accord, 1990. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Mid-Year Conference, 1991 Mar. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Washington Office reports, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - general information, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - NASDA/USDA Task Force, 1991 Aug. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Food and Agriculture Exposition, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Agriculture Week, 1991 Mar. (Box 8)
    - National 4H Engineering, 1991. (Box 8)
    - State-Provinces Agriculture Accord, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Nursery Industry Study/Survey, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of Conservation Districts - newsletter, 1988-1991. (Box 8)
    - Organic Standards Advisory Board, National, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Organic (general information), 1991. (Box 8)
    - President's Enterprise Initiative, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Private Property Rights Act of 1991, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Pennfield, 1991. (Box 8)
    - People to People Citizen Ambassador, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Personnel and Training, Dep.t of, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Planning/Development, 1987. (Box 8)
    - Peanuts (general information), 1991. (Box 8)
    - Purcell, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Potatoes - States/Canada, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Prompt reports, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Radiation Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 8)
    - REAP - Blackstone, 1991 July. (Box 8)
    - Rail Industry Access, 1990. (Box 8)
    - Register of Regulations, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Records Management, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Referendum - Virginia Small Grain Producers, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Referendum - Sweet Potato, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Regional meetings, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Recycling Collection Program, 1989-1991. (Box 8)
    - Retail Food Special Advisory Comm, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Rural Virginia Development, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program, 1991. (Box 8)
    - ROCCO Open House, 1991 Sept. (Box 8)
    - Rural Development Committee, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Rural Rehabilitation Trust Fund, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Salmonella Outbreak (Glenwood Farm), 1991. (Box 9)
    - Salmonella Enteritidis, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Seafood Task Force, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Sole Source Procurement, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Southside Virginia Produce Cooperative, 1988-1991. (Box 9)
    - State Land Evaluation Advisory Council (SLEAC) and Dept. of Taxation, 1991 Sept. (Box 9)
    - Solicitation of Contributions, 1989-1991. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1991 Sept. (Box 9)
    - State Agency Group Luncheon, 1989-1991. (Box 9)
    - State Milk Commission, 1989-1991. (Box 9)
    - Soybean Check Off Program, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Certified Seed Board, 1990. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Seafood Industry Task Force / Study, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
    - State agencies and departments (general information), 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Water Control Board, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Legislators, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Southern States Cooperative, Inc., 1990. (Box 9)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
    - Southside Economic Development Commission, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Rural Development Councils, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Society, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Society of Association Executives, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Sweet Potato referendum, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Internal Auditor, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Surface Transportation Assistance, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Savings Bond Campaign, 1987-1991. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1991. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board meeting, 1991 Mar 21. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board meeting, 1991 May 16. (Box 9)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Board meeting, 1991 July 18. (Box 9)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA, 1991. (Box 9)
    - United States Senate, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Fair Committee, 1988-1991. (Box 9)
    - Social Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 9)
    - State Fair Commonwealth Day, 1991 Oct 1. (Box 9)
    - Southern Legislative Conference, 1991 July 20-24. (Box 9)
    - Southwest Virginia Agricultural Association, 1985-1991. (Box 9)
    - Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA) meeting, 1991 June 15-19. (Box 9)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 1985-1986. (Box 10)
    - Southern United State Trade Association (SUSTA), 1991. (Box 10)
    - Third World (general information), 1986-1990. (Box 10)
    - Laboratory Service Task Force, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Study of Program Area, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
    - Task Force on Food Safety, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Task Force on Cooperation with Land Grant Universities, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
    - Tobacco Market Opening, 1991 July 31-Aug 1. (Box 10)
    - Tobacco Appreciation Day, 1991 June 4. (Box 10)
    - Tributyltin (TBT), 1991. (Box 10)
    - Take Pride in America, 1990. (Box 10)
    - Treasury, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Travel, 1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA - Packers and Stockyards, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Tobacco (general information), 1991. (Box 10)
    - Toxic Substances Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 10)
    - University of Virginia (UVA), 1988-1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA Budget Summary, 1992. (Box 10)
    - USDA - Farmers Home Administrtion, 1988-1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA (general information), 1991. (Box 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives - News releases, 1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA - Virginia Food and Agricultural Council, 1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA - Forest Service, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Conservation and Recreation - News releases, 1991. (Box 10)
    - USDA - Soil Conservation Service, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Retail Merchants Association, 1988-1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Equine Center Foundation, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farmers Market, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Drought Monitoring Task Force, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Association of Fairs, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Agriculture Expo, 1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Agriculture Commodity - Newsletter, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
    - Food Service Manager Certification, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, Inc., 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Activities/Blacksburg, 1991 July 11-12. (Box 11)
    - Virginia State University, 1989-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Water Resources Research Center, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Liaison Office, 1986-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Crop Improvement Association, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Agricultural Development Authority, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Cattlemen's Association, 1988-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - VPI and SU (Virginia Tech) (general information), 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Dairymen's Association, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1988-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Alliance for Public Service, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia State Dairy Goat Association, 1987-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Potato and Vegetable Growers Association, 1982-1990. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Ag-Chemicals and Soil Fertility Association, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Farmer, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia State Horticultural Society, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Horse Council, Inc., 1989-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Council of Farm Cooperatives, 1988-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Executive Institute, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Walk America, 1990. (Box 11)
    - Yoseph Elkana (Israeli Extension), 1989-1991. (Box 11)
    - Waste Management, Dept. of, 1989-1991. (Box 11)
    - Wetlands, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Wisconsin Public Intervenor, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Powell River Project, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Review/Internal Audit, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Morton W. Libarkin (Home Operation), 1991. (Box 12)
    - Hill Brothers (Lynchburg), 1991. (Box 12)
    - Meat and Poutry Inspection Program, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Marketing Division, 1991. (Box 12)
    - Cost of Living - Foreign Based Employees, 1991. (Box 12)
    - Classification Activity Report, 1991. (Box 12)
    - Turner, Clinton V., 1991. (Box 12)
    - Administration (Blankenship) #2, 1991. (Box 12)
    - Memos to Division Directors, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, Inc., 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Monthly reports, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Division of Pair, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Division of Marketing, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Bright Flue-Cured Tobacco Commission, 1979-1991. (Box 13)
    - Sweet Potato Referendum, 1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board, 1986-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Egg Board, 1989-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Cattle Industry Board, 1989-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia State Apple Board, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Soybean Commission, 1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Cattle Industry Board meeting, 1991 Apr 15. (Box 13)
    - Virginia State Peanut Commission, 1979-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Pork Industry Board, 1991. (Box 13)
    - State Seed Potato Commission, 1974-1991. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Sweet Potato Commission, 1977-1991. (Box 13)